Donald E. Hattin Media Materials 1959/2016 PC006
Test - Paleontology Collection
Donald E. Hattin Media Materials
1959-2016
Test - Paleontology Collection
Hattin, Donald E.
PC006
15 cubic feet Seven boxes, 24 x 15 x 10 1/4"; 26 folder boxes, 11.5 x 6.5 x 5.5"; bulk of documents
Donald E. Hattin served as a professor of geology at Indiana University from 1954 to 1995. His collection consists primarily of materials relating to his research, published works, and teaching files.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research. Advance notice required.
Biographical Note
Hattinâs work is in paleoecological studies of Upper Cretaceous benthic organisms, especially including oysters, cirripeds, and rudists. He also does taxonomic studies of Upper Cretaceous benthic organisms, including oysters, anomiids, and cirripeds.
In addition he studies Cretaceous stratigraphy of the Western Interior Basin, with emphasis on depositional environments, cyclicity, basinwide correlation of carbonate-rock intervals, and stratigraphic manifestations of contemporaneous tectonic uplift.
Hattin also collaborates with Katrina Gobetz (James Madison University) on the causes of recent rodent gnawings on rocks of Mississippian and Cretaceous age.
Arrangement
The Hattin collection is organized into five series: media, correspondence, reprint, map, and personal collection
Scope and Content Note
Media includes open-reel video tape, 2x2 slides, negatives, photographs, graphs, drawing, and original material for publication in teaching, talk, specimens, and locality.
Correspondence consists of Hattin's routine administrative correspondence and etc. compiled by author.
Reprint consists of Hattin's reprints, publications, and manuscripts curated by author.
Map consists of locality map with detailed notes by Hattin.
Personal collection consists of slides, negatives, prints, letters, and postcard.
Acquisition Information
Inherited from the author.
Geology–Kansas; Geology, Stratigraphic—Cretaceous; Geology—Guidebooks; Paleontology—Cretaceous; Paleontology, Stratigraphic; Paleoecology; Paleoclimatology; Paleoceanography; Cirripedia; Hattin, Donald E.
- Media, 1959-2016
  - Metal boxes containing slides, located on top of cabinet (Loose-drawer 1)
    - G334 – 54 slides (Loose-drawer 1)
    - Talks – 151 slides (Loose-drawer 1)
    - Greenhorn Formation – 154 slides (Loose-drawer 1)
    - British and Amex Chalk – 75 slides (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1)
    - Kansas Global Chalk – 173 slides (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1, Envelope 1)
    - KD/KG – 73 (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1, Envelope 1)
    - Niobrara, Kansas – 137 slides (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1, Envelope 1)
    - Pychdonite talks – 71 slides (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1, Envelope 1)
    - 1979 talk – 96 slides (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1, Envelope 1)
    - Europe – 254 slides (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1, Envelope 1)
    - Widespread Ls Beds KGH – 165 slides (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1, Envelope 1)
    - Dev/Penn – 102 slides (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1, Envelope 1)
    - Colorado – 8 slides (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1, Envelope 1)
    - Regional – 241 slides (Loose-drawer 1, Folder 1, Envelope 1)
  - Loose slides (Drawer 1)
    - Geology of Bahamas – 18 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Oklahoma Geobiology – 44 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Sed Structure – 37 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Processes – 64 slides (Drawer 1)
    - All San Sal – 38 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Indiana Geology, Mosquito Marsh, Fossils (2m facies concept) – 44 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Grotto Reef (Vicki's lecture) – 24 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Carbonate Sedimentology – 24 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Miscellaneous sedimentary reefs – 13 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Minerals and rocks (ign sed mm) – 74 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Geology of SS (caves, dunes, beaches, lakes, lagoon) – 50 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Gullets Creek – 16 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Global Chalk (extra) – 20 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Beach, reef, and undersea – 47 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Bridge Creek – 78 slides (Drawer 1)
    - Organisms – 70 slides (Drawer 1)
  - Loose negatives and prints (Drawer 2)
    - Unidentified loose negatives (Drawer 2)
    - Subject-specific negatives (Drawer 2)
      - Cirripeds prints with negatives (Drawer 2)
      - Niobrara Fossils - prints and negatives (Drawer 2)
      - Graneros Fossil Negatives - prints and negatives (Drawer 2)
      - Dakota Fossils - prints and negatives (Drawer 2)
      - Some 1965 GDBK Negatives (Drawer 2)
      - Wed. Paper #5 Hattin #1 - negatives of assorted specimens (Drawer 2)
  - Manuscript materials (Drawer 3)
    - Subject-specific manuscript materials (Drawer 3)
      - KE S.E.M. - prints with negatives and detailed notes (Drawer 3, Folder 1)
      - Figures: Smoky Hill Bulletin - prints with negatives (Drawer 3, Folder 2)
      - Prints with negatives and detailed notes (Drawer 3, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous manuscript materials (Drawer 3, Folder 3)
      - Greenhorn Data Compilation (Drawer 3, Folder 4)
      - Coprolites (Drawer 3, Folder 5)
      - Paper or manuscript D.E. Hattin (Drawer 3, Folder 6)
      - Lariber (Drawer 3, Folder 7)
      - Gnawed Rocks (Drawer 3, Folder 8)
      - GSA talk receipts (Drawer 3, Folder 9)
      - Rodent Rocks Final (Drawer 3, Folder 10)
      - Comparative autonomy notes (Drawer 3, Folder 11)
      - Depositional Environment of the Wreford Megacyclothem (Lower Permian) of Kansas (Drawer 3, Folder 12)
      - The Megascopic Invertebrate Fossils of The Carlile Shale of Kansas Mineralogy (Drawer 3, Folder 13)
  - Thematic Materials (Drawer 4)
    - Laminations and photos - prints and negatives (Drawer 4, Folder 1)
    - Laminations and photos - prints and negatives with notes (Drawer 4, Folder 2)
    - Fecal Pellets II and Photos - prints and negatives with notes (Drawer 4, Folder 3)
    - Stramentidae and photos - prints and negatives with notes (Drawer 4, Folder 4)
    - Streoscan Negatives / KGH and prints (Drawer 4, Folder 5)
    - Callixylon Borings Photos - prints and negatives (Drawer 4, Folder 6)
    - Greenhorn Photos Mottled Beds Maps, X-Section, Photomicrographs (Drawer 4, Folder 7)
    - Field Photos - prints and negatives with notes (Drawer 4, Folder 8)
    - Transparent Scales For Negatives and Photomicrographs - negatives for measurement (Drawer 4, Folder 9)
    - SEM - Bridgecreek Samples Negatives and Photos - photos and negatives with notes (Drawer 4, Folder 10)
    - Preservation, Photos, Maps, etc. - photos and negatives with notes (Drawer 4, Folder 11)
    - Anomia slides - script for 1987 GSA meeting (Drawer 4, Folder 12)
    - Wedge Diagram Negative (Drawer 4, Folder 13)
    - Bentonites Photos - prints with notes (Drawer 4, Folder 14)
    - Substrate Talk - negatives with notes (Drawer 4, Folder 15)
    - Corrections to New Mexico and Colorado (Charts) Sections - stratigraphy drawings (Drawer 4, Folder 16)
    - Coprolites Photos and Negatives - prints, negatives, graphs, reprints and notes (Drawer 4, Folder 17)
    - Interregional Model Photos, Negatives, and Charts – photos, negatives, feedback, original figures for publication (Drawer 4, Folder 18)
    - Photos and Chart + Correlations / Greenhorn Paleontology - list of specimens locality (Drawer 4, Folder 19)
    - Ciirripeds as Epizoans / Negatives - NSF proposals, review correspondences (Drawer 4, Folder 20)
    - Niobrara / Photo and negative - description of Niobrara vertebrate fossils on display in Hays Kansas State College Museum, prints, and negative of invertebrate (Drawer 4, Folder 21)
    - Envelope - Photos - deteriorated photos (Drawer 4, Folder 22)
    - Dakota Paleontology / Charts, Photos, Drawings (Drawer 4, Folder 23)
    - Pycnodonte N.S.P. / Photo and photomicrography - Pycnodonte, Gryphaea, and Exogyra related reprints, prints, and micromicrography Hattin Denmark Slides - 6 slides (Drawer 4, Folder 24)
    - Calcispheres (photos) - calcispheres photos and related reprints (Drawer 4, Folder 25)
    - Guatemala (overheads) - transparencies and notes (Drawer 4, Folder 26)
    - Black Shale (Pictures, Photos) - reprints, drawings, charts, notes, photos (Drawer 4, Folder 27)
    - Grotto - Final Draft (original version) (Drawer 4, Folder 28)
    - Grotto Data - reprints and notes (Drawer 4, Folder 29)
    - Grotto Photos, Charts - photos, charts, drawings, notes, reprints (Drawer 4, Folder 30)
    - Grotto Photos, Negatives, Charts - photos, negatives, charts, notes, drawings by students (Drawer 4, Folder 31)
    - Greenhorn Rudist (overheads) - reprints, transparencies, drawings, notes, photos, correspondence (Drawer 4, Folder 32)
    - Loose prints of microphotographs, locality, and ammonites on cardboard (Drawer 4, Folder 33)
    - Volcanoes in eruption set – 27 slides (Drawer 4, Folder 34)
    - Locality prints on cardboard and locality map negatives (Drawer 4, Folder 35)
    - Fairport cirripedes - Prints and negatives (Drawer 4, Folder 36)
    - Stramentidae SPEM print - Prints and negatives (Drawer 4, Folder 37)
    - Loose notes and photomicrograph prints (Drawer 4, Folder 38)
    - C X-1200 20µ 24mm - Prints and negatives 1974 (Drawer 4, Folder 39)
    - Carb X300 100µ 30mm - Prints and negatives 1974 (Drawer 4, Folder 40)
    - C X600 50µ 30mm - Prints and negatives 1974 (Drawer 4, Folder 41)
    - C X1500 20µ 30mm - Prints and negatives 1975 (Drawer 4, Folder 42)
    - C X270 100µ 27mm - Prints and negatives 1974 (Drawer 4, Folder 43)
    - C X3000 10µ 30mm - Prints and negatives 1975 (Drawer 4, Folder 44)
    - Ophiuroid Spares - Prints (magnification X6 - X15) (Drawer 4, Folder 45)
    - Niobrara SEM PRINTS W/ SCALES - Prints (magnification 10μ-50μ) (Drawer 4, Folder 46)
    - Graneros field photos - copies - Locality prints (Drawer 4, Folder 47)
    - NEGATIVES FOR K 6PBK - Specimens and locality map negatives (Drawer 4, Folder 48)
    - Greenhorn Outcrop of photos 1963 - Locality prints with locality info at the back of prints (Drawer 4, Folder 49)
    - Graneros fossils - geology - Prints of specimen figures on reprints and real specimens pictures from the depository of specimen (Drawer 4, Folder 50)
    - Carlile negative localities - Locality map negative (Drawer 4, Folder 51)
    - Book copy job - Reprints negatives (Drawer 4, Folder 52)
    - Greenhorn Photomica X40 - negatives and reprints (Drawer 4, Folder 53)
    - Plates NAPC II - Reprints negatives (Drawer 4, Folder 54)
    - Carlile Photomicrographs - Photomicrographs prints, X40 (Drawer 4, Folder 55)
    - PUBLICITY PHOTOS, FROM KODACHROMES - Sheet film negative of Hattin(?) collecting fossil (Drawer 4, Folder 56)
    - Rudist - Prints, negatives, correspondence letter, notes on radiolitids/rudist (Drawer 4, Folder 57)
    - C X160 16mm=100µ - Print and negatives 1973 (Drawer 4, Folder 58)
    - Beachwork illustrations - Print and negatives (Drawer 4, Folder 59)
    - Rock Polished NIOBRAR PETROLOGY NEGS.-PRINTS - Print and negatives (Drawer 4, Folder 60)
    - 27 Loose cardboard with prints (Drawer 4, Folder 61)
  - Thematic Materials cont'd (Drawer 5)
    - Carbonate substrates (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
    - Miss karst charts, drawings (Drawer 5, Folder 2)
    - Waldron (Drawer 5, Folder 3)
    - NM Geological Society (Drawer 5, Folder 4)
    - Hattin Siemus Plates (Drawer 5, Folder 5)
    - Smoky Hill (Drawer 5, Folder 6)
    - Regurgitate negative (Drawer 5, Folder 7)
    - Dakota Macroinverts, plates and negatives (Drawer 5, Folder 8)
    - Cret. Global Illus. rough drafts (Drawer 5, Folder 9)
    - Fairport Cirriped negatives (Drawer 5, Folder 10)
    - Chalk facies trans. (Drawer 5, Folder 11)
    - Chalk dep. Model (Drawer 5, Folder 12)
    - Finished chalk illus. (Drawer 5, Folder 13)
    - Western Interior Seaway biostratigraphy chart (Drawer 5, Folder 14)
    - Graneros paleontology drawings (Drawer 5, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous greenhorn drawings, charts (Drawer 5, Folder 16)
    - Photos – field and general (Drawer 5, Folder 17)
    - Lodgement probe drawing (Drawer 5, Folder 18)
    - Pellets #1 photos, negatives (Drawer 5, Folder 19)
    - Vascoceras photos and negatives (Drawer 5, Folder 20)
    - Cirriped manuscript photos and negatives (Drawer 5, Folder 21)
    - Pictures, drawings, negatives (Drawer 5, Folder 22)
    - Plates – Hattin and Warren (Drawer 5, Folder 23)
    - Loose papers and photos in desk (Drawer 5, Folder 24)
    - Gulf coast chalk prints (Drawer 5, Folder 25)
    - Anomia photos (Drawer 5, Folder 26)
    - Chalk report photos and plates (Drawer 5, Folder 27)
    - East Germany (Drawer 5, Folder 28)
    - Everhart (Drawer 5, Folder 29)
    - F (contains correspondence) (Drawer 5, Folder 30)
    - Pictures – Feldman (Drawer 5, Folder 31)
    - Greenhorn prints of line drawing (Drawer 5, Folder 32)
    - Greenhorn cyclothem negative (Drawer 5, Folder 33)
    - Grotto prints (Drawer 5, Folder 34)
    - Mauck photos (Drawer 5, Folder 35)
    - M photos (Drawer 5, Folder 36)
    - Niobrara field photos (Drawer 5, Folder 37)
    - San Salvador thin sections (Drawer 5, Folder 38)
    - Negative (Drawer 5, Folder 39)
    - Reagan Oysters (Drawer 5, Folder 40)
    - Original figures (Drawer 5, Folder 41)
    - Hasenmueller (Drawer 5, Folder 42)
    - Niobrara polished surfaces (Drawer 5, Folder 43)
    - Regional Aspects Field Photos (Drawer 5, Folder 44)
    - Regional Aspects Line Drawing Prints (Drawer 5, Folder 45)
    - KGS Bulletin 178 Graneros (Drawer 5, Folder 46)
    - KGH Field Photos 1966 J. Cocke (Drawer 5, Folder 47)
    - Greenhorn Field 1962 (Drawer 5, Folder 48)
    - Fossil Prints and Negatives Carlile (Drawer 5, Folder 49)
    - 1974-75 G135 Epizoans (Drawer 5, Folder 50)
    - KGH Colorado and New Mexico 1979 (Drawer 5, Folder 51)
    - Bridge Creek Megafossil negatives (Drawer 5, Folder 52)
    - U.K. Substrates Negs. Prints (Drawer 5, Folder 53)
    - Hatcher Ranch Photos 1971 (Drawer 5, Folder 54)
    - Archer and Hattin (Drawer 5, Folder 55)
    - Strat Column (Drawer 5, Folder 56)
    - Smoky Hill line drawing (Drawer 5, Folder 57)
    - Greenhorn Fossil Prints (Drawer 5, Folder 58)
    - Photomicrographs Niobrara Petrology (Drawer 5, Folder 59)
    - Greenhorn SEM's (Drawer 5, Folder 60)
    - G-420 Kansas Lecompton Megacyc. (Drawer 5, Folder 61)
    - G-420 Kan. Hoosergully and Grenola (Drawer 5, Folder 62)
    - Greenhorn Photomicrographs Negatives (Drawer 5, Folder 63)
    - 1 manila envelope labeled, "Greenhorn outcrop photos" (Drawer 5, Folder 64)
    - Pycnodonte negatives and prints (Drawer 5, Folder 65)
    - Carlile Fossil Prints (Drawer 5, Folder 66)
    - Photos of Canada Museum Bulletin 29 (Drawer 5, Folder 67)
    - Surface with St. Louis limestone (Miss.) S.W. Indiana (Drawer 5, Folder 68)
    - Trace photo talk at Iowa City Negatives – manila folder (Drawer 5, Folder 69)
    - Reprintable Negatives for 1971 AAPG article (Drawer 5, Folder 70)
    - Dakota Fossil Prints (Drawer 5, Folder 71)
    - Miscellaneous unmounted fossil transparencies (Drawer 5, Folder 72)
- Correspondence, 1959-2016
  - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Correspondence sorted alphabetically by name or subject (Box 1)
      - Cobban (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Dhondt (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Elder, [William (Recommendations and correspondence)] (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Fac. Comm Awards (Faculty Community awards) (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Global Sedimentology [International Workshop] correspondence, papers from workshop (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Grand Cayman: Literature on biography and ecology of mollusks on the Cayman Islands from Western Illinois University (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Guatemala Physiography (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Cirriped – Japan, Hokkaido (Corresponds with Hawakaya + photo) (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - H- Envelope with images of Cephalopods from Dodge City, Kansas (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Kirkland (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - New Chairman (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - New Mexico- The American Journal of Science, The stratigraphy of the Mt. Taylor region, New Mexico by HW. Shimer and Mildred E. Blodgett, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Paleocurrent / Greenhorn (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Powell (University of Idaho) (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Research projects (1 hand written page) (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Trustees Retirement Party 1955-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Rushdi Said (Fax correspondence) (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Rockers Correspondence on Niobrara Rudist and Durania ((2 Letters)) (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Steve Stow Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Research (Handwritten notes) (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Stewart (Natural History Museum of Los Angeles) Information and Letter (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - SGE: Grad School Application (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Storr, [Manfred] - East Germany (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Scott (Amoco) (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Sigma Gamma Epsilon (Skits and Screwball Award) (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Watney, [W. Lynn]- Sea Level (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Young, [Keith]- University of Texas (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Loose materials – Reviews, annual report, meetings and etc. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and documents relating to colleagues (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Teaching Files, 1959-2016
  - Class Notes – G-705: Biogeology Lecture -1982 (Box 2)
    - Current G705 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Cret. Kansas lecture (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Chalk seminar (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Chalk seminar 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - G705 II (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - G705 III (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - G705 Chalk #5 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Chalk 6 G705 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Chalk seminar 6 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Chalk seminar Nov 12 1993 #7 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Chalk seminar Dec. 3 G705 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - G705 Chalk seminar Dec. 16 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Seminar – Stratigraphy (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - G705 Fall '64 Dep. Environ. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - G705 stratigraphy seminar 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Sept., Oct., Nov. 1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - G705 Week of Nov. 12 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - G705 Week of Nov. 19 1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Week of Dec. 3 1992 G705 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - G705 Week of Dec. 10 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 4 untitled folders (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Biogeology lecture 1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Class Notes – G-014 – G-703 (Box 3)
    - Loose transparency slides and book on the principles of benthic community analysis (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Dodd G104 1st 4 lectures (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Geology G014 syllabus (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - G334 Chem of PT of CaCO3 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - G420 (1990) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Hattin G420 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - G511 Geol. Time Class (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - G511 lecture Lilly (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - G511 revised lecture #15A (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - G511 revised: lecture #17 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - G511 revised Chalk lecture #16 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - G512 Cret. Of Nova Scotia and G512 L.K. ALT and Gulf Coastal Plain (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Plate tectonics G554 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - All G575 information (6 folders put together) (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Class notes (16 folders concerning San Salvador and tropical locations put together) (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Horowitz seminar G701 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Exploring ancient seas lecture G701 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Gary's vert. paleo 1978 G703 class (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Seminar topics (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Seminar trophic anal bivalves Fall '79 (G703) (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - G703 Paleoecology seminar (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Paleoecology seminar 1963-1964 G703 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Paleoecology seminar 1967-1968 G703 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - G703 Paleoecology (Cretaceous) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Paleoecology seminar Spring 1965 – G703 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Field Trip and Talk Materials (Box 4)
    - Documents concerning 1993 G-420 Field Trip to New Mexico and Colorado (Box 4)
      - Photomicrographs from 1990 G-420 field trip (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Readings G-420 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Day 1 May 14 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Waivers (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Day 2 May 15 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Day 3 May 16 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Day 4 May 17 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Day 5 May 18 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Day 6 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Day 7 May 20 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Day 8 May 21 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Day 9 May 22 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Day 10 May 23 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Day 11 May 24 (Mon) (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Day 12 May 25 (Tues) (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Day 13 May 26 (Wed) (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Tax-Free No. (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Day 14 May 27 (Thurs.) (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - 3 travelogues (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Talk materials (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - History of Geology Bibliography (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Report on widespread LS Beds (includes APPG 1979 Talk) (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Abstracts/ Talk Outlines (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Fairport Talk Cirriped Paleoecol. (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - G.S.A. Talks 61-61 and cyclic symp. Ms. (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Paper at 1985 –GSA Meeting Orlando, Florida (overhead) (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Smoky Hill Rudist Talk (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - 1996 Chalk Talk (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - 1979 Talk (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - AAPG Bridge Creek Talk (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Fribourg (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - McCormick Creek Paleokarst (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Reprint, 1959-2016
  - Broad subject reprints (Box 5)
    - Cobban selected papers (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Corals and Reefs (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correlation charts (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "American Chalk Deposits: A Synthesis" and "History of Geology" By Donald Hattin (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Sedimentary structure (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Subject-specific reprints (Box 6)
    - Erico Cretaceous – Mediterranean region (Box 6)
      - Rudist data Cañon City (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Preservation, Rudists, Nomenclature, Shelf Sea Chalk (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - G511 Berea data (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Shelf Sea Chalk synthesis (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Preservation tables (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - My revision of nomenclature (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - This is a paper I'm working on Jan. 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - #53A Silurian Carbonates (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Triassic, Jurassic, Mesozoic (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous loose articles and journals (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Exogyra (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Loose articles and one book at the back (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Preservation figs. (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Stephenson 1914 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Exogyra M.S. (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Exogyra – Marker 4-5 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Exogyra papers/ref. list (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Exogyra (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Chalk I (Box 7)
    - New Zealand Chalk (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - North Sea (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Oligocene example (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Lublin translation (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Netherlands (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Poland (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Romania (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Scotian shelf (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Morocco Chalk (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Sweden (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Syria (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Tunisia (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Turkey (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - U.K. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - USSR (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - U.S. East Gulf Coast (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - E. U.S. Shelf Chalk (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - U.S. West Gulf Coast (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Western Interior (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Tables (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Chalk update (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Notes on Chalk units for global Chalk (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Chalk II (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Chalk papers (Box 8)
      - English Chalk localities (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Characteristics of British and U.S. Western Interior Chalk (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Diagenesis (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Milankovitch Cycles (Box 8, Folder 4)